Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- H-HE, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 796)
  Correspondence with John W. Hacker; R.A. Haddock; Charles J. Haden; Joyce Haedt; John A. Hagemann; Isabel Haggerty; J.P. Haggerty; Guy Lynn Hague; Laura L. Hahn; Georgia E. Haines; Alice Hale; Ellis R. Benson; Half Moon Bay Union High School; J.E. Hall; James S. Hall; Mary E. Hall; R.G. Hall; Paul Halladay; J.W. Hallock; Alfred R. Hamilton; Hamilton Union High School; Hamilton Union High School; Helen Hammerten; A.R. Hampsey; Hamtramck Public Library; Glen W. Handley; Hanfort Joint Union High School; Hanford Union High School; Lalita Hannah; Howard Hanson; Virginia Hannon; S.B. Hansell; Elmer Hansen; Gregson Harder; Jean Hardin; Alice P. Harkey; Kate Harkness; Harlem Book Company; Herbert J. Harper; James C. Harper; Maria Daugherty Harper; Kate Harrington; Harris Alvin Theatre; Credo Fitch Harris; Richard L. Harris; Grace H. Hall; Board of Public Education, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; Board of School Directors; Floyd E. Harshman; Herman M. Hart; Martha Hart; Board of Public Education, Hartford, Connecticut; The Board of Education; Hartford Public High School; Thomas R. Hartley; harvard University; The President and Fellows of Harvard College; Julia Harwood; Edwin M. Hasbrouck; Cecille Haser; Carl V. Hass; Mildred Hassman; Julian H. Hatch; M.E. Hatcher; Margaret E. Hathaway; Guy Hatley; Hawkes Free Children's Library; Cora Nance Haynes; Hayward Union High School; Charles Haywood; Frank Haywood; Alice Willigerod; John Heck; Adriane Heim; Hazel Helleck; Hemet Union High School; Henderson Public Library; Beulah R. Henry; Ada Hensel; Harry D. Henshel; Harry D. Henshel; Margaret Hermann; A.M. Herron; Maurice Herzberger; Anna E. Heuer
- HF-HZ, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 797)
  Correspondence with Robert C. Hibbs; M. Hieronyme; Georgia Higgins; Charles Hill; Edna M. Hill; Rosamond Van Camp Hill; Helen M. Hillard; Augusta Hiller; Hilmer Union High School; John Hladinec; The Hobby Shop; Russell Hobdy; Russell Hobdy; Free Public Library, Hoboken, N.J.; Fletcher Hodges; Francis T. Hodges; Allen Hodshire; Kenneth Hoel; Isabelle H. Hoersch; Charles A. Hoffman; Earl Hoffman; Lois Hoffman; James Hogan; John Hogan; Lura Hoke; Dorothy Holcomb; John Wheeler Holland; Sarah E. Holland; New London Academy; Milton C. Hollingsworth; A.L. Holmes; Wyatt Holmes; Holtville Union High School; Carnegie Library of Homestead Pennsylvania; J.I. Hommel; M.A. Hoover; Russell Hopkins; Hopland Union High School; F.C. Hopton; Robert Hough; Letha House; Houston Public Library; Ella W. Howard; Glenna Howard; Howard Memorial Library; Howard University Library; W.A. Howe; Sara Howell; Duncan Howlett; Samuel E. Hudson; Horatio Hughes; Catherine Highes; Hughson Union High School; Humbolt School; Louise Humphreys; Huntington Beach, Union High Scholl; Henry Huntington Library and Art Gallery; The Huntington Memorial Library; L.B. Huss; Helen Huth
- Howard, John Tasker, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 798)
  Correspondence with John Tasker Howard of Glen Ridge, NJ. In 1932 Howard was a musicologist with one book to his credit. He earned additional income by lecturing around the country and hosting a radio show. Howard and Lilly met for the first time in Nov, 1932. By Dec. 1932 Howard was working on the Foster biography, receiving a small stipend from Lilly for support during his research. Howard was rapidly accepted by the Foster Hall staff. The biography was published in Jan. 1934. The correspondence during this year is rich with gossip as well as opinions and reviews of the many plays and movies which were being produced that season. Howard was having legal difficulties at this time. His publishers were withholding permission for Howard to dramatize the biography which he hoped to have Gene Raymond direct. The 1935-38 correspondence holds an enormous quantity of letters about the Foster house controversy; verification that Foster lived in Hoboken; Howard's arrangements of Foster; Maskell Ewing's death. Also a lot of notes between Howard and Hodges pointing out errors in the biography.
- I, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 799)
  Correspondence with Idaho State Historical Society; State of Idaho; Idaho University Library; Imperial Valley Union High School; Imperial Union Elementary Schools; Owens Valley Union High School, Independence, California; Indiana Society of Chicago; Indiana State Library; Indiana University Library; Indianapolis Engraving Company; Inglewood Union High School; International Records Agency; Indian Wells Valley Union High School, Inyokern, California; Ione Union High School; State Historical Society of Iowa; Iowa State Library; Irvington High School; Irvington Free Public Library; W.J. Irving; Isaacs Book Exchange
- Indianapolis Photo Company, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 800)
- J, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 801)
  Correspondence with Donald G. McKay; Jackson Union High School; Board of Public Education, Jackson, Mississippi; Anne Jackson; Mabel Jackson; Martha Jackson; Will Jackson; Board of Public Education, Jacksonville, Florida; Jacksonville Public Library; Corinne Jamar; Florine James; Mary James; C.C. Jefferson; Herbert Jene; Board of Public Education, Jersey City, New Jersey; Free Public Library, Jersey City; Jervis Library; Irene Jesse; Willard Rouse Jillson; Marie Jane Joffre; Einar Johanson; Johns Hopkins University Library; Juanita Johnson; Conrad Johnson; H.B. Johnson; Helen P. Johnson; Kathryn Johnson; Keen Johnson; Mary K. Johnson; Mildred P. Johnson; Robert W. Johnson; E.V.D. Johnston; Johnstown Center; Ira B. Jones; Sally Jones; Jones and Laughlin; B.F. Jones Memorial Library; Elliot P. Joslin; E.P. Joslin; Marcellus Joslyn; Dwight S. Juckett; Juilliard School of Music; Julian Union High School; Alice G. Jung; Juniata College
- KA-KE, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 802)
  Correspondence with Station KDKA; Joseph B.G. Kaczynski; William Kamin; James J. Kane; Mabelle Glenn; Kansas City Public Library; Kansas State Teacher's College; Kansas Wesleyan University; Kappelhoff Art Studio; M.L. Kappelhoff; B. Kassal; Keasler and Clark; Louise Kebler; Arthur J.S. Keene; Lloyd Keepers; Henrietta Keiger; Ruby Keller; Joseph A. Kelley; Eddie G. Kelly; Marrie G. Kelly; Arnold Kelm; Kelseyville Union High School; Caroline Rose Kennedy; Florence Kennedy; George Kennedy; James L. Kennedy; Kentucky Historical Society; University of Kentucky Library; F.P. Keppel; Kerman Union High School; Frank Kern; John Kern; William Kern; John D. Kerr; Walter C. Kerr; Emma B. Kessler; W.E. Kessler; Weir C. Ketler; Frances Ketterer
- KF-KZ, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 803)
  Correspondence with C.R. Kilgore; Anna M. King; Frederick King; King City Union High School; Kingsburg Joint Union High School; Noreen Kingsley; V.G. Kinnaird; A.L. Kinnear; Agnes L. Kinnear; Frederick J. Kinsman; Kathryn Kinville; Mary Kipling; Charles L. Kirk; Jane Kirker; E.E. Kirkwood; Merritt Kistler; Louis P. Kleber; Max Kleckner; Berneda Klick; Helen Kline; Richard Kline; Paul Klohr; George Knapp; Betty Knauss; Strickland Kneass, Jr.; Jess Knighton; Paul Knobloch; Barbara Knott; Sarah Gertrude Knott; William F. Knox; Board of Public Education, Knoxville, Tennessee; Louis Knudsen; Kohl, Taylor, and Fischer; Margaret Koliadko; J.E. Konkle; William G. Kottman; Dick Kovar; Dorothy A. Kram; Fred. Kranz Music Co.; Virginia Krick; Evelyn Kroemer; Wm. F. Kugel; Mabel Kunkel; Dorothy Kunz; Katherine Kusterer
- L-Ll, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 804)
  Correspondence with Maud Ward Lafferty; James S. Lanahan; Clear Lake Union High School, Lakeport, California; Morris Lamberton; Antelope Valley Joint Union High School, Lancaster California; P.C. Land; S.M. Langsdale; Board of Public Education, Lansing, Michigan; Annie LaRue; Frank Lathrop; Laton Joint Union High School; Lillian Lott; Laughlin Memorial Free Library; Dorothy Laur; Lisette Lautenschlaeger; George H. Bell; Harold Lavine; Lois Law; Lawrence College; Lawrence Conservatory of Music; The Lawrenceville SChool; Lawrenceville Times-Gazette; Olive Lawry; Betty Jane Lawson; Phyllis Lazansky; Ethel C. Leahy; E.C. Leahy; Alma H. Lear; Henry Leding; Philip Ledoux; University of Leeds; Lloyd Leeper; Betty Leeson; Leevining Union High School; Bess E. LeFevre; J.R. Leggate; Clyde Ogden; Le Grand Union High School; Lehigh University; Stephen M. Lehmer; E. Leitheuser; Lemoore Union High School; Ellen LeNoir; A.E. Leonard; Vito Leone; Lester Levy; Ralph Lewando; Fay E. Lewis; Glenn R. Lewis; Harrison Lewis; Lewiston Public Library; Board of Public Education, Lexington, Kentucky; Lexington Public Schools; The Library of Congress; J.M. Lichty; Betty Lidler; David H. Light; Florrie Jean Lightfoot; Eli Lilly; Lincoln Union High School; Sylvia Lindberg; Linden Union High School; Frank J. Lindner; Lindquist; A.S. Linhart; Lion's Club of East Liberty; R.G. Little; Live Oak Union High School; Livermore Union High School; George Livingston Jr.; The Lloyd Library
- LM-MZ, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 805)
  Correspondence with Daniel Lockett; Lodi Union High School; Lompoc Union High School; Lone Pine Union High School; National Geographic Society; George Washington Junior High School, Long Beach, California; Long Island University; Longan, W.L.; Clarence Loomis; Rosalie W. Looney; City of Los Angeles; John Adams Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Louis Pasteur Junior High School; Samuel Gompers Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Belvedere Junior High School, Los Angeles; William McKinley Junior High School, Los Angeles California; Luther Burbank Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Ralph Waldo Emerson Junior High School; Central Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Lafayette Junior High Achool, Los Angeles, California; Robert Louis Stevenson Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Mt. Vernon Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Washington Irving Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Horace Mann Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Hollenbeck Junior High School; John Muir Junior High School; Berendo Junior High School, Los Angeles, California; Thomas Starr King Junior High School; John Burroughs Junior High School; Hubert Howe Bancroft Junior High School, Los Angeles; Brett Harte Junior High School, Los Angeles; Belvedere Junior High School; Louis Pasteur Junior High School; Berendo Junior High School; William McKinley Junior High School; Thomas A. Edison Junior High School; John Adams Junior High School; William McKinley Junior High School; Joseph LeConte Junior High School; Los Angeles Public library; West Side Union High School, Los Banos, California; Los Gatos Union High School, Los Gatos, California; Silvia Lostegaard; Sister M. Louis; Louisiana State University; Board of Public Education, Louisville, Kentucky; Miss Louthry; Maude W. Lovelace; Winfred H. Low; W.H. Lowdermilk and Company; Edna Lowe; Arthur G. Butzbach, Lower Lake Union High School; F. Lowman; M.S. Lowrey; Loyaola University; Luce's Press Clipping Bureau; Esther Ludke; Mrs. Frank H. Ludwigs; Robert W. Lull; Lulu E. Lundquist; Keith Lundy; Frank Luther; L. Russell; Jean Lyda; Edna Lysne
- Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 806)
- Lilly, (Dorothy Black), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 807)
- Mc, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 808)
  Correspondence with Fall River Joint Union High School, McArthur, California; John McCans; John J. McCarthy; Katherine McCartney; Mildred McCartney; E.S.H. McCauley; Vincent McConaughy; G.A. McCormick; Elizabeth McCay; J.W. McCoy; W.D. McCoy; Juanita McCracken; Wiley McCrary; Thomas C. McCune; W. Richard McCutchon; Bernie L. McDaniel; Bernice L. McDaniel; Bernice L. McDaniel; David Earl McDaniel; G.A. McDaniel; Josephine A. McDevitt; Wm. McDevitt; J.M. McDonald; Edward MacDowell; Aline McFerron; Adelia McGarry; Josephine McGaw; L.H. McGhee; F.J. McGinnis; Robert MacGowen; Jane E. McGray; Ernest F. McGregor; A.B. McGrew; Margaret McInerey; W.B. McIlvaine; Gertrude McIver; Betty McKee; Wm. C. McKinley; A. McKinstry; H.L. McKnight; Edgar McKown; J.T. McLamore; Billy McLean; C.A. McLean; Harry McMarr; William McMaster; L.B. McMullen; Gerald McMurtry; James B. McNair; Marcella McNanamy
- MacAlester College, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 809)
  Elizabeth MacFarlane; Katherine W. Mackey; Shirley Ann Mackie; Madera Union High School; Joseph E. Maddy; Board of Education, Madison Wisconsin; Anne Mcaul; James Madison; Modesto Madrid; Mabel Mahoney; Harry Majforth; Harry Malforth; Maine Historical Society Library; Maine State Library; University of Maine Library; N. Malym; Butch Malpas; James Manchester; Edward Manczuk; Ruth Mandone; Manistee City Public and School Library; Elsa W. Mansmann; Manteca Union High School; William C. Maple; George Lee Marable; Georgie Lee Marable; A.J. Marino; A.J. Marino; Marion Clare; Rose Marclowe; A.N. Marquis; Harriett S. Marsh; H.R. Marsh; Bradley Marshall; Munson Marshall; Margretta Martin; Margaretta M. Martin; Roscoe B. Martin; W.K. Martin; Arthur H. French; Martinez Public Schools; Public Library, Martinsville, Indiana; Maryland Historical Society; Maryland Historical Society; Marysville Union High School; Mason City Public Library; Orpha S. Mason; Grayson W. Massie; Charles Masso; A.H. Mathias and Company; Marguerite Matthew; H.N. Mawhinney; Frank B. Maxfield; Maxwell Union High SChool, Maxwell, California; Darlene Maxwell; Mary Louise May; Arthur E. Mayer; Eleanor M. Means; W.C. Mearns; Louise Meckelmann; Pauline Meddling; The Medford Public Library; Lucy Medz; C.T. Meek; Arthur Meighen; Arthur Meighen; Mabel A. Meissner; Norine Mellette; Mellon Institute; Henry Melnik; W.F. Melton; Wightman F. Melton; Dorothy Meltzer; Board of Public Education, Memphis, Tennessee; Board of Education, Memphis City Scools; Mendocino Union High School; Meneely and Company; Merced Union High School; The Public Library, Mercersburgh, PA; Jane Merrill; Roger B. Merriman; W.B. Merritt; Claybron W. Merriweather; Eli Messenger; Kathryn Messer; Jullian Messner; L.W. Mesta; Ellen May Meyer; Dora Meyersburgh; Julia Meyersburgh
- MF-MZ, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 810)
  Correspondence with Board of Public Education, Miami, Florida; The Miami Herald; University of Miami; Williams Michels; University of Michigan; Arthur M. Mickelson; A.M. Mickelsen; Middletown Union High School; Anne Midgette; Alfred Midgley; E.J. Miles; Catherine R. Miller; Charles Miller; Christina Miller; Elmer E. Miller; Irvin Miller; Jeraldine Miller; John Miller; Josephine H. Miller; June Marie Miller; Lore Miller; Louisa Miller; Rose Ann Miller; Beverly Miles; Geneva Millington; Mima R. Milliron; C.Q. Mills; Mills College Library; Librarian of Mills College; Milton Public library; Board of Education, Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Public Library, Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Board of Education, Minneapolis, Minnesota; Minneapolis Public Library; University of Minnesota Library; South Fork Union High School, Miranda California; Mississippi State Library; University of Mississippi; Missouri State Library; The State Historical Society of Missouri; Helen Mistrick; A.D. Mitchell; Alexander Mitchell Library; E.B. Mitchell; Grace Mitchell; H.C. Mitchell; Harland C. Mitchell; Roy O. Mitchell; Frances C. Moffitt; Hilda C. Mohr; Lester Ramon Mohr; W.B. Mollard; Alice Molle; Monoe Public Library; School District of Monongahela, PA; Monrovia-Arcadia-Duarte Union; Monrovia City Schools; Evelyn Montag; Montana State College Library; Historical Society of Montana; University of Montana Library; Sabina Montao; Public Schools, Montclair New Jersey; Montebello, California; Monterey Union High School; Board of Public Education; Montgomery Public Schools; Douglass Montgomery; Edwin F. Montgomery; Margaret H. Montgomery, Thomas Montgomery; Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts; Board of Public Education, Montpelier, Vermont; Montville Township; Board of Education, Montville, N.J.; Jane Mooney; Alice Moore; E.E. Moore; Fred Moore; Irene Moore; Lois Moore; Mary E. Moore; Scott Moore, Jr.; Morrpark Memorial Union High School; Moorpark Memorial High School; Bolly R. Moran; Mary Morgan; Nina L. Morgan; Live Oak Union High School, Morgan Hill, California; Henry Morris; Winifred A. Morris; Virginia Morrison; Nick Morone; J.A. Morton; Norma Moschini; Annie R. Moseley; Catherine Moukous; Mount Saint Mary's College; Alexandrian Free Public Library, Mount Vernon, Indiana; Mountain View Union High School; Raymond Mowers; P.C. Mukerji; Joseph Muller; Edith Muller; Alice E. Millins; Muncie Public Library; Ralph Munn; David V. Murdoch; John A. Murdock; Elizabeth Murphy; L.C. Murr; Elsie Murray; Foster Murray; Grace Muse; The Museum Shop; Music Education Publications; Musical Courier; Musical Forecast; Muscogee Public Library; Margaret Myers
- Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 811)
  Correspondence with Evelyn Foster Morneweck of Detroit, MI, Morrison Foster's daughter. Lilly first contacted her in 1931. For an undisclosed sum she added some of the most vital pieces to the Collection: Foster's manuscript book, Foster's wallet, etc. In 1932-33, Mrs. Morneweck rendered invaluable assistance to J.T. Howard as he prepared America's Troubadour. During this time she also began The Chronicles of Stephen Foster's Family which wouldn't be completed until 1944. Over the years the correspondence grew to several hundred pieces a year. Many items are factual in nature--checking genealogies, etc--but some letters are filled with rumors, gossip and speculation. Lilly and Morneweck became close friends and were quite open with one another. The 1934 folder, for instance, contains fascinating opinions of Henry Ford as he became embroiled in the White Cottage fiasco. Hodges weeded these files after the moved to Pittsburgh, feeling that certain letters shouldn't be made available to the public. Other letters, because of the valuable factual material they contain, were removed from this correspondence and placed in the collection.
- N, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 812)
  Correspondence with Emelie M. Nafis; Louis F. Nafis; Napa Union High School; Billy Nasch; E.C. Nash; Board of Public Education, Nashville, Tennessee; Stanley Nathanson; National Broadcasting Co.; National Carloading Corporation; Sweetwater Union High School, National City, California; National Library of Scotland; Nebraska State Historical Society; John D. Neefus; Southwest Junior High School, Nestor, California; Nevada State Library; Peggy Neville; Public Schools of New Brunswick New Jersey; New Castle Free Public Library; New England Conservatory of Music; New Hampshire State Library; Board of Education, New Haven, Connecticut; New Jersey historical Society; University of New Mexico Library; Orleans Parish School Board; Board of Education, Borough of Brooklyn; Board of Education, Borough of the Bronx; Board of Education, Borough of Queens; Board of edcuation, Borough of Richmond; Board of Education, New York City; New York Historical Society; New York Public Library; New York State Library; New York University; Board of Public Education, Newark, New Jersey; The Newberry Library; Rexford Newcomb; Ray N Newell; Orestimba Union High School; Newport Harbor Union High School; Board of Public Education, Newport News, Virginia; The People's Library, Newprt Rhode Island; Isla A. Newton; Thomas Flight Nichols; Edward Abbe Niles; John Jacob Niles; Samuel Nisenson; Robert P. Noble; Bennett Nolan; Lena B. Nofcier; J. Bennett Nolan; Helen F. Noon; Charles H. Norburn; Board of Public Education, Norfolk, Virginia; Norfolk Public Schools; Norfolk Public Library, Edith B. Norris; North Carolina State Library; University of North Carolina Press; Mary T. Bobbitt; North Dakota Agricultural College; State Historical Society, Bismarck, North Dakota; Grant Union High School, North Sacramento, California; North Texas State Teachers College; Northwestern University Library; Excelsior Union High School, Norwalk, California; J.E. Norwood; Grant Union High School, North Sacramento, California; North Wildwood Public Schools; J.J. Northcott; Library of the Universit of Notre Dame; Lucy Nulton; Warren Nuss; Roger A. Nye
- O, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 813)
  Correspondence with Oakdale Union High School; Oakdale Free Library; Oakland Public Schools; Lincoln Junior High School, Oakland, California; Elmhurst Junior High School, Oakland, California; Herbert Hoover Junior High School, Oakland, California; Frick Junior High School, Oakland, California; Woodrow Wilson Junior High School, Oakland California; Hamilton Junior High School, Oakland Califronia; Lockwood Junior High School, Oakland, California; Claremont Junior High School, Oakland, California; Goldengate Junior High School, Oakland, California; Garfield Junior High School, Oakland, California; Prescott Junior High School, Oakland, California; Westlake Junior High School, Oakland, California; Bret Harte Junior High School, Oakland, California; Oakland Public Schools; Mary Oberholtzer; Ruth Oberholtzer; Oberlin College; F.M. O'Brien; Mary Edith O'Brien; William J. O'Brien; Oceanside-Carlsbad Union High School; John O'Conner; The Odd Shop; Margorie Oellig; Carnegie Free Library, Ogden, Utah; Oglebay Institute; Oglethorne University; Oglethorpe University, Georgia; Ohio State Archaeological historical Society; Nordhoff Union High School, Ojai, California; Oklahoma State Library; University of Oklahoma Library; Alice M. Olander; Old Magazine Mart; Annabelle Oliver; David Olmsted; Omaha Public Library; Omaha Public Schools; Elsie Omohundro; J.T. O'Neal; Chaffey Union High School, Ontario, California; Orange Union High School; Charles Orchard; Oregon Historical Society; University of Oregon; Orland Joint Union High School; B.H. Ornoff; Oroville Union High School; Orosi Union High School; Orosi California; Osterhout Free Library; Irma D. Osti; Henry Ostrom Jr.; Township Library, Otsego, Michigan; Anna E. Overton; Ruth Owen; Joseph T. Owens; W.D. Bannister; Oxnard Union High School
- P-PE, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 814)
  Correspondence with Pacific University; Geraldine Padgett; L.B. Padgett; Lucille B. Padgett; Joseph Palkovitz; F.L. Palmer; Frank R. Palmer; G.A. Palmer; David Starr Jordan Junior High School, Palo Alto, California; Pan-American Union Library; The Panama Canal Library; Lillian Parah; Margaret Parke; Charles Franklin Parker; Minette S. Parker; Pauline Parker; Parlier Union High School, Parlier, California; Fay Patlowe; Helen Parrish; Margaret Parrish; Florence Fisher Parry; Ruth M. Parson; Walter E. Parson; Louella O. Parsons; Charles W. Elliot Junior High School; William McKinley Junior High School, Pasadena, California; George Washinton Junior High School, Pasadena, California; Pasadena Public Library; Frosta W. Pasley; Paso Robles, California; Patterson, Union High School; Alfaretta Patterson; Carolyn D. Patterson; Clara S. Patterson; Patterson Library; Ed Patton Music Co.; Margaret Patton; Charlene Paul; Alice Payne; Gregory Pavlovsky; Gregory Pavlovsky; George Peabody College for Teachers; Virginia Pearson; J.M. Pedley; William I. Pelz; Tempe Pemberton; Charles Pendlebury; Carolyn Penn; E.W. Penn; Dorothy Pennekamp; Vivian Penner; Grace Pennock; The Historical Society of Pennsylvania; Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Public Instruction; Pennsylvania State College; Pennsylvania State Library and Museum; Perris Union High School; Katherine Perry; Peru Public Library; Pescader Union High School; Milton A. Peterson; Petaluma Junior High School; Mattole Union High School, Petrolia, California; C.M. Pettit; William Pettit; Mary E. Pew
- PF PZ, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 815)